Guide to the Service Employees International Union Local 585 Records, 1966-1989 AIS.1982.14
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Chapter Files: Education, I.
  - School Districts, 1.
    - South Butler School District - Dues/Membership, 1971-1973 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - South Butler School District - Contracts, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - South Butler School District - Negotiations, 1975-1977 (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - South Butler School District - Contracts, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - South Butler School District - Miscellaneous, 1971-1974 (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - South Park School District - Organization, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - South Park School District - Negotiations, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - South Park School District - Contracts, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - South Park School District - Negotiations, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 70)
    - South Park School District - Contract, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 71)
    - South Park School District - Negotiations, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 72)
    - South Park School District - Contract, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 73)
    - South Park School District - Chapter Officers, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 74)
    - South Park School District - Dues/Membership, 1971-1973 (Box 13, Folder 75)
    - South Park School District - Seniority Breaks, 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 76)
    - South Park School District - Grievances/Meet & Discuss, 1971-1975 (Box 13, Folder 77)
    - South Park School District - Scheduling/Hours, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 78)
    - South Park School District - Lotsko Discipline, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 79)
    - South Park School District - Proposed Contract, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 80)
    - South Park School District - Negotiations, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 81)
    - South Park School District - Negotiations, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 82)
    - South Park School District - Proposed Contract, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 83)
    - South Park School District - Contract, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 84)
    - South Park School District - Salary/Seniority Lists, 1971-1977 (Box 13, Folder 85)
    - South Park School District - George Vellmer Holiday Grievance, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 86)
    - South Park School District - Miscellaneous, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 87)
    - Southeastern Greene School District - Organization, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 88)
    - Southeastern Greene School District - Contracts, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 89)
    - Southeastern Greene School District - Negotiations, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 90)
    - Southeastern Greene School District - Contracts, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 91)
    - Southeastern Greene School District - Negotiations, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 92)
    - Southeastern Greene School District - Contracts, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 93)
    - Southeastern Greene School District - Job Postings (Box 13, Folder 94)
    - Southeastern Greene School District - Gabler Shift Change/Reprimands, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 95)
    - Southeastern Greene School District - Dues/Membership, 1971-1973 (Box 13, Folder 96)
    - Southeastern Greene School District - Negotiations, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 97)
    - Southeastern Greene School District - Contracts, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 98)
    - Southeastern Greene School District - Miscellaneous, 1971-1977 (Box 13, Folder 99)
    - Southmoreland School District - Organization, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 100)
    - Southmoreland School District - Negotiations, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 101)
    - Southmoreland School District - Contract, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 102)
    - Southmoreland School District - Negotiations, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 103)
    - Southmoreland School District - Contracts: NEA-Teachers, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 104)
    - Southmoreland School District - Contract, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 105)
    - Southmoreland School District - Managerial Intimidation, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 106)
    - Southmoreland School District - 585 News article, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 107)
    - Southmoreland School District - Negotiations, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 108)
    - Southmoreland School District - Contract, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 109)
    - Southmoreland School District - Officers, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 110)
    - Southmoreland School District - Job Bidding/Seniority Grievances, 1973-1978 (Box 13, Folder 111)
    - Southmoreland School District - Dues/Membership, 1971-1973 (Box 13, Folder 112)
    - Southmoreland School District - Meet and Discuss, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 113)
    - Southmoreland School District - Vignalli Disciplines and Workmens Compensation, 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 114)
    - Southmoreland School District - Negotiations, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 115)
    - Southmoreland School District - Contracts, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 116)
    - Southmoreland School District - Salary/Seniority Lists, 1971-1977 (Box 13, Folder 117)
    - Southmoreland School District - Grievances, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 118)
    - Southmoreland School District - Dues/Staff Assignments, 1975-1978 (Box 13, Folder 119)
    - Southmoreland School District - Hours/Assignments/Unemployment, 1974-1978 (Box 13, Folder 120)
    - Southmoreland School District - Membership Meetings, 1972-1975 (Box 13, Folder 121)
    - Southmoreland School District - Accumulated Sick Days, 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 122)
    - Southmoreland School District - Miscellaneous, 1972-1977 (Box 13, Folder 123)
    - Trinity School District - Organization, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Trinity School District - Negotiations, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Trinity School District - Proposed Contract, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Trinity School District - Negotiations, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Trinity School District - Contracts: Custodial, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Trinity School District - Membership/Dues, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Trinity School District - School Meeting Place, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Trinity School District - Night Shift Temperature, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Trinity School District - Negotiations, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Trinity School District - Contract: Clerical, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Trinity School District - Membership/Dues, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Trinity School District - Organization: Clericals: Aids, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Trinity School District - Brautigam Discipline, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Trinity School District - Officers/Factionalism, 1971-1975 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Trinity School District - Organization: Bus Drivers, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Trinity School District - Custodial Wage Reopener Agreement, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Trinity School District - Contracts: Clericals/Aids, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Trinity School District - Contracts: Clericals/Aids, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Trinity School District - Contracts: Clericals/Aids, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Trinity School District - Negotiations, 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Trinity School District - Dues/Memberships, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Trinity School District - Salary/Seniority Lists, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Trinity School District - Tennant Seniority Case, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Trinity School District - McWee Gender Discrimination Bid, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Trinity School District - PSEA Teacher Contract, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Trinity School District - Negotiations, 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Trinity School District - Negotiations: Secretaries and Aides, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Trinity School District - Organization: Cafeteria, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Trinity School District - Miscellaneous, 1973-1977 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Turtle Creek School District - Employee Handbook/List, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Turtle Creek School District - Directories, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Turtle Creek School District - Proposed Wages, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Turtle Creek School District - Disciplines, 1971-1974 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Turtle Creek School District - Dues Record Cards, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Turtle Creek School District - Contracts, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Turtle Creek School District - Dues/Membership, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Turtle Creek School District - Officers, 1971-1973 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Turtle Creek School District - Organization/East Pittsburgh Merger, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Turtle Creek School District - PSEA Raid, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Turtle Creek School District - Miscellaneous, 1970-1973 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - United School District - Membership Cards, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - United School District - Directory, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - United School District - Organization/Amended Certification (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - United School District - Negotiations, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - United School District - Contracts, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - United School District - Negotiations, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 46-47)
    - United School District - Proposed Contract, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 48-49)
    - United School District - Organization Cafeteria, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - United School District - Negotiations: Cafeteria, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - United School District - Authorization Cards: Cafeteria, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - United School District - Decertification Bid: Independent, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - United School District - Duncan 7 Hour Day, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - United School District - Salary/Seniority Lists, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - United School District - Miscellaneous, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Washington School District - Individual Contract, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Washington School District - Organization, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - Washington School District - NEA Teachers Proposal, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - Washington School District - Contract, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - Washington School District - Dues/Membership, 1971-1973 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - Washington School District - Negotiations, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - Washington School District - Negotiations, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - Washington School District - Proposed Contract, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - Washington School District - Contract, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - Washington School District - Salary/Seniority Lists, 1970-1974 (Box 14, Folder 66)
    - Washington School District - Seniority Status, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - Washington School District - Chapter Funds, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - Washington School District - Chapter Officers, 1971-1973 (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - Washington School District - Re-Opener Attempts, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 70)
    - Washington School District - Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - Washington School District - Negotiations, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 72)
    - Washington School District - Contracts, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 73)
    - Washington School District - Cafeteria Benefits Arbitration, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 74)
    - Washington School District - Cost of Living Increase, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 75)
    - Washington School District - Holiday Pay Grievance, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 76)
    - Washington School District - Lay-Offs, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 77)
    - Washington School District - Seniority Lists and Dispute, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 78)
    - Washington School District - Miscellaneous, 1971-1978 (Box 14, Folder 79)
    - West Jefferson School District - Organization, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 80)
    - West Jefferson School District - Organization, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 81)
    - West Jefferson School District - Organization: Clerical, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 82)
    - West Jefferson School District - Negotiations, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 83)
    - West Jefferson School District - Contracts: Custodial, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 84)
    - West Jefferson School District - Contracts: Cafeteria, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 85)
    - West Jefferson School District - Contract Supplement: Custodial, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 86)
    - West Jefferson School District - Salary/Seniority/Employment Lists, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 87)
    - West Jefferson School District - Dues/Membership, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 88)
    - West Jefferson School District - Women's Equal Wages, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 89)
    - West Jefferson School District - Cafeteria Sub-Contracting, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 90)
    - West Jefferson School District - Authorization Cards: Clerical, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 91)
    - West Jefferson School District - Negotiations: Clerical, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 92)
    - West Jefferson School District - Contracts: Clerical, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 93)
    - West Jefferson School District - Dues/Membership, 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 94)
    - West Jefferson School District - Negotiations: Custodial, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 95)
    - West Jefferson School District - Contracts: Custodial, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 96)
    - West Jefferson School District - Negotiations: Cafeteria, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 97)
    - West Jefferson School District - Contracts: Cafeteria, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 98)
    - West Jefferson School District - Negotiations: Clerical, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 99)
    - West Jefferson School District - Salary/Wage/Seniority Lists, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 100)
    - West Jefferson School District - Contracts: Clerical, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 101)
    - West Jefferson School District - Gloria Webb Wage Increase, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 102)
    - West Jefferson School District - Sick Leave Grievance, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 103)
    - West Jefferson School District - Substitute Duty for Part-Timers Grievance, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 104)
    - West Jefferson School District - Payroll Method Dispute, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 105)
    - West Jefferson School District - Miscellaneous, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 106)
    - West Mifflin School District - Pre-Union Period, 1963-1970 (Box 14, Folder 107)
    - West Mifflin School District - Organization, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 108)
    - West Mifflin School District - Negotiations, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 109)
    - West Mifflin School District - Contracts, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 110)
    - West Mifflin School District - Negotiations, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 111)
    - West Mifflin School District - Negotiations, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 112)
    - West Mifflin School District - Negotiations/Strike, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 113)
    - West Mifflin School District - Contracts, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 114)
    - West Mifflin School District - Negotiations, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 115)
    - West Mifflin School District - Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 116)
    - West Mifflin School District - Hiring/Resignation Notices, 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 117)
    - West Mifflin School District - Hiring/Resignation Notices, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 118)
    - West Mifflin School District - Hiring/Resignation Notices, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 119)
    - West Mifflin School District - Membership, 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 120)
    - West Mifflin School District - Membership, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 121)
    - West Mifflin School District - Chapter Officers, 1971-1976 (Box 14, Folder 122)
    - West Mifflin School District - Disciplines/Firings, 1974-1977 (Box 14, Folder 123)
    - West Mifflin School District - Meet and Discuss/Job Posting Issues, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 124)
    - West Mifflin School District - Secretaries' Summer Hours Grievance Arbitration, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 125)
    - West Mifflin School District - Dorris Lynn Classification Arbitration, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 126)
    - West Mifflin School District - Clerical Wage Adjustment Request, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 127)
    - West Mifflin School District - Membership/Salary Lists, 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 128)
    - West Mifflin School District - Mazzarise Seniority Grievance, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 129)
    - West Mifflin School District - Wahrenberger Longevity Increment, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 130)
    - West Mifflin School District - Board Salary Repayment Demands, 1971-1976 (Box 14, Folder 131)
    - West Mifflin School District - Wage Memo of Agreement, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 132)
    - West Mifflin School District - Miscellaneous, 1971-1975 (Box 14, Folder 133)
    - Western Area Vo-Tech School District - Authorization Cards, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Western Area Vo-Tech School District - Membership Applications, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Western Area Vo-Tech School District - Organization, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Westmoreland Intermediate School District - Organization, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 4-5)
    - Westmoreland Intermediate School District - Contract, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Westmoreland Intermediate School District - Negotiations, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Westmoreland Intermediate School District - Contract, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Westmoreland Intermediate School District - Information Booklet, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Westmoreland Intermediate School District - Job Description/Classifications, 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Westmoreland Intermediate School District - Wage/Benefits List, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Westmoreland Intermediate School District - Negotiations, 1973-1975 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Westmoreland Intermediate School District - Contracts, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Westmoreland Intermediate School District - Contracts, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Westmoreland Intermediate School District - Salary/Seniority lists, 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Westmoreland Intermediate School District - Unit Clarification, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Westmoreland Intermediate School District - Grievance, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Westmoreland Intermediate School District - Disciplines/Firings, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Westmoreland Intermediate School District - Dues/Membership, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Westmoreland Intermediate School District - School Board Minutes, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Westmoreland Intermediate School District - Job Bidding, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Westmoreland Intermediate School District - NEA Raid, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Westmoreland Intermediate School District - Miscellaneous, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Organization: Custodial, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Organization: Cafeteria, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Maintenance Department Work Descriptions and Items, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Directories, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Contracts: Custodial, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Negotiations, 1971-1973 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Contracts: Custodial, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Contracts: Cafeteria, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Contract Addendum: Cafeteria, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Grievances, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Dues/Membership, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Meet and Discuss, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Membership Lists, 1970-1973 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Officers Elections, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - NEA Teacher Contract, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Group Insurance and Dental Plans, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Student Handbook, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Negotiations, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Cafeteria Contract Amendments, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Negotiations, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 43-45)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - School Board Contract Proposal, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Contracts: Cafeteria, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Contracts: Custodial, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Negotiations/Ballots, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Contracts: Cafeteria, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Membership Meeting Notices, 1972-1977 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Salary/Seniority Lists, 1971-1978 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Officers Elections/Factionalism, 1974-1977 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Grievances, 1974-1978 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Meet and Discuss, 1974-1976 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Dues/Membership, 1974-1977 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Cafeteria Contracting Out, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - CETA/Unemployment, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Negotiations, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Contracts: Custodial, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - Wilkinsburg School District - Miscellaneous, 1971-1977 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Colleges and Universities, 2.
    - California State University - Organization: Cafeteria (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - California State University - Blue Cross Plan, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - California State University - Salary/Salary Lists and Benefits (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - California State University - Negotiations, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 4-5)
    - California State University - Pennsylvania Public Employees Retirement System Handbook (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Community College of Allegheny County - Organization, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Community College of Allegheny County - Organization, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 8-10)
    - Community College of Allegheny County - Organization, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Community College of Allegheny County - Health and Life Insurance Plans (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Community College of Allegheny County - Payroll Spread Sheet (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Community College of Allegheny County - Negotiations, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 14-16)
    - Community College of Allegheny County - Contract, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Community College of Allegheny County - Confidential Employees Unit Clarification (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Community College of Allegheny County - Staffing Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Community College of Allegheny County - Staffing Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Community College of Allegheny County - Disciplines/Firings: A-M, 1973-1975 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Community College of Allegheny County - Disciplines/Firings (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Community College of Allegheny County - Labor-Management Meet and Discuss, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Community College of Allegheny County - Membership Lists and Addresses, 1973-1975 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Community College of Allegheny County - Officers and Stewards, 1973-1975 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Community College of Allegheny County - Job Reclassification, 1973-1975 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Community College of Allegheny County - Factionalism, 1973-1975 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Community College of Allegheny County - Negotiations/Contract, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Community College of Allegheny County - Negotiations, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 29-31)
    - Community College of Allegheny County - Negotiations (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Community College of Allegheny County - Negotiations, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 33-36)
    - Community College of Allegheny County - Contract (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Community College of Allegheny County - Staffing Reports, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 38-39)